[sweet airy music]
[soft gentle music]
[Yeon-su] They say that the more
that you try and run away from the past,
conversely the more
you eventually become trapped in it.
[soft gentle music]
Yeon-su's grandmother picks her up
because she doesn't have any parents.
Why don't you have any parents, Yeon-su?
You know that means
you can't play house with us.
Who says I wanna play house with you?
[Yeon-su] Makes perfect sense.
Why do you care so much about her?
That self-centered princess
doesn't like you,
she doesn't even know you exist.
She's right. Think about it.
Yeon-su's never bothered
treated us or anything.
We always bought her stuff.
Still, it wasn't like she asked us
to buy her any of those things.
It's called being shameless.
She still accepted them every single time.
[Yeon-su] Even after all this time…
[sniffles]
I really wish that…
[soft sob]
I was only poor enough
to the point that I…
I could at least handle it.
…I may look different now…
but I'm still that helpless girl,
lost inside that playground.
Don't know why,
but my life's always been that way.
[fragile music]
[soft sob]
Yeon-su…
Let's stop doing this.
[shaky breathing]
Always worrying about not getting hurt…
I…
…and then ending up
hurting the people I love.
I don't
see the point
in the two of us being together.
All 'cause I had an inferiority complex.
["There For You" by Kim Na Young playing]
Enjoy your food, guys.
- Thank you.
Hold on a sec.
[Yeon-su] Moving forward
pretending like everything was fine
hanging onto the hope
that things would get better somehow.
And that was when it happened.
["There For You" playing]
INCOMING CALL
CHOI UNG
It seems to be a memory
that Ung doesn't recall.
Ung called me that night.
It was the first time
after we'd broken up.
Just tell me the reason
why we can't be together.
That's all, Yeon-su.
Because if you don't, at least
give me one good reason,
I'm gonna have no choice
but to hate everything about myself.
I'll have to just accept that I'm
someone who deserves to be abandoned.
[shaky breathing]
["There For You" continuing]
[deep exhale]
It's not you, it's me. I'm going through…
a rough patch.
It's just, my family is going
through a tough time.
I can't afford dating right now.
And I don't want you to…
I mean, I don't expect you to
get consumed by all this misery.
[Yeon-su sobs over phone]
That's why.
[scoffs]
[sighs]
Seriously, is that all?
[Ung sighs]
It would have been better to just say
you don't love me anymore or something.
[Ung] Because if that's why…
if that's the reason
you're breaking up with me…
that's just ridiculous.
["There For You" continuing]
Why did we even break up back then?
[Yeon-su] Just like that.
That's what the past does to you.
The more you try to run away from it,
the more it just traps you in.
It'll find you no matter what you do.
And eventually, you'll end up
making the same mistakes.
EPISODE 14
LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL
What's this all of a sudden?
It's just, I've always been curious.
We'd always argue, break up, and then
get back together. Over and over again.
It never bothered me that much…
[Ung scoffs]
…because I always knew that
we'd never break up for real anyway.
Except for that day.
[Ung] I wasn't so sure anymore.
It felt like you were
really desperate to break up with me.
So why? I wanna know the reason.
Back then I…
I was getting very exhausted.
You know how busy I was part-timing,
making ends meet and writing resumes.
What's the point in bringing up the past?
Why don't we just forget about all that?
The only thing that matters
is we're back together.
Hmm.
It's getting late.
I should be getting home now.
Grandma's been upset
'cause I've been coming home late.
She's gonna flip.
- I'll drop you off.
- It's okay. I can just call a cab.
I'll be fine. You just got home.
You need to rest. Get some sleep.
Yeon-su.
Take care, okay?
Hmm.
[gentle vulnerable music]
[sleepy groan]
[Ja-gyeong] You're home.
What about dinner? Have you eaten already?
What's wrong?
Did something bad happen to you?
[exhales sharply]
Nothing. Everything's fine.
Yeon-su…
You know,
that jerk came by the house today.
I know.
Well, I didn't call him. I promise you.
That boy came on his own.
So what did you say to him?
You scold his ears off again?
Of course I didn't.
You think I'm like
some kind of pitbull or something?
[chuckles softly]
[Ja-gyeong] By the way, Yeon-su.
[Yeon-su] Yes?
[Ja-gyeong] Did… I mean,
back then when you broke up with him,
did you… did you break up with him
because of our tough situation?
Huh?
Did you…
break up with him
because you were shouldering
everything by yourself?
What do you mean? Of course not!
Why would you even think that?
We just had a big fight
and then ended things.
Which shouldn't be a surprise, seeing as
I have a nasty temper just like you.
Can you stop
thinking about silly stuff like that?
[Yeon-su groans softly]
This is the warmest spot in the world.
Hey, Grandma, can I sleep here with you?
It's been a while.
[soft caring music]
[sniffs]
[inhales]
If you have something to say,
please, I wanna know.
Uh, sure…
Although, Yeon-su, that girl told me
not to say anything to you.
I'm only telling you this because you
decided to come here on your own.
Okay.
You really like my granddaughter,
don't you?
I can guarantee you,
I like her a lot more than you think.
Okay. Good. Then nothing else matters.
I'm asking you to stand by her,
no matter what.
- But, you don't need to worry about--
- What I mean is,
I want you to be by her side always.
And not just for now,
but as long as you can.
Please don't let
my granddaughter feel alone.
[gentle music]
Ever since Yeon-su was a little girl,
I was the only person
she had that she could rely on.
[Ja-gyeong] It's been a lonely existence
as she had neither
a true family nor friends.
But it didn't matter,
she carried all the burden
all by herself whatever it was.
When our family fell apart
and we had no money to recover,
that young girl
pushed forward single-handedly.
[breathes in shakily]
In any case,
she hasn't had many things in life.
Except you, you've always had
a special place in her heart.
So please don't make her
feel lonely anymore.
Stay by her side
no matter what happens, will you?
Okay. Don't worry, I will.
[sighs in relief]
I know this is a lot for you,
this is a heavy burden
that I'm placing on your shoulders.
But I don't have a choice.
She's suffered so much
and I'm asking for your help
because I'm not gonna be here forever.
What I'm saying is that she needs you.
["Home" by Janet Suhh playing]
Can I ask you something?
Just what exactly happened to your family?
Huh?
["Home" by Janet Suhh continues]
All right. Let's see here.
WITH UNG
Holy crap! Oh my goodness, Ji-ung,
you almost gave me a heart attack.
Hey, stop that. You know darn well
you're not supposed to film this.
Sorry, it's been a while.
So I need to capture every little detail.
You're yanking my chain. We both know
you shouldn't be filming this.
[Ho] Stop it. Turn that off.
- [Yeon-ok] Honey, what are you doing?
- What? No. What do you mean?
Seems like
you're gonna pocket all of that.
I wasn't gonna pocket anything.
I was just standing here
doing some bookkeeping.
We had a deal.
I told you, no more fishing rods.
- Yes. Of course.
- There's no more room at home for that.
- [Ho] Exactly, yep.
- Okay. Give me that.
I was not gonna take this.
Can you calm down?
- Give me that.
- I was gonna buy some ingredients
down at the market.
Ji-ung, can I check your camera for a bit?
I just need to see how much this guy took.
- Hey, turn this off.
- Show me the last few seconds. Step away!
- Turn it on.
- [Ho] There's nothing to see.
- Ho! You all set, brother?
- [Yeon-ok gasps]
[Chang-sik] Look,
I'm all geared up over here.
- Shut up!
- Why you liar!
Don't tell me you're going fishing again!
- [Ho] Ow!
- [Yeon-ok] You are unbelievable!
Come on, let's go outside. Move it!
[Ho] What the heck are you talking about?
[phone buzzing]
Yeah?
No, I was about to leave.
Why does he wanna see me
so early in the morning?
All right. I got it.
- You got some high ratings.
- Hmm. So I've heard.
People really enjoyed it.
- Uh-huh. So I've heard.
- Jezus, you're annoying.
But now that you're done.
Let me use her now.
I'm guessing your shows always flop
because you lack basic common sense.
She's not an object.
She's not something you can just use.
[Dong-il] Kim Ji-ung!
Good morning.
Hey, what took you so long?
I've been waiting for you over here.
I mean, it's only been
a few hours since I clocked out.
Producer Kim, I know you're thankful
and extremely grateful.
So, would you like to repay my kindness
by swearing your absolute loyalty to me?
I told you this was gonna be
a successful show.
It's been 54 weeks since we made it big
from the first episode.
How come you don't look too happy? What?
Did we shut down a show or something?
Aren't you at least
a little happy with the result?
Yeah, I'm ecstatic.
What's with you, dude?
Chae-ran, can you tell me
what's going on with this guy here?
He hasn't slept much,
so I'm guessing he must be exhausted.
Nah, he's protesting.
All right then, fine.
You can do
a peaceful environmental documentary
just like you wanted after this.
You're allowed to bask in the glory,
you know that?
- I'm eating with the director today, so--
- I'm okay. Forget it.
"Okay, forget it," my ass.
Pissy, pouty, proud little punk.
You notice,
he's even more annoying now, huh?
Oh, by the way, what do those two think?
Ung and Yeon-su.
I'm not sure. I haven't asked them.
Wow, those two
are gonna be even more famous now.
You see, that's the power of the media,
so we gotta be responsible.
[Dong-il] More people will recognize them.
What if the other TV stations
invite them to guest for their shows?
Please. They're not that famous.
But if they do become famous,
the people around them
are gonna start reaching out to them
for one reason or another.
See, that's what the media does.
It attracts unnecessary attention
as a consequence.
Tell them to ignore anyone
they've lost touch with.
Or suddenly showing up at their doorstep
to ask for a handout.
Make sure they're aware
of those comebacks.
- Dong-il.
- Hmm?
I know you're excited right now
just because we finished the thing,
but we're not that successful.
- Say what?
- Really, it was just the first episode.
Yeah, but still.
When is Ms. Lee arriving?
In 20 minutes. Probably a traffic jam.
- Okay, tell me when she gets here.
- Okay.
[cheeky music]
Gosh.
He's so annoying but he's really good.
So adorable you just wanna bite him.
I should try that. He'd have a huge fit.
What is it?
Huh? No, it's nothing really.
Are you gonna be working today?
Of course. The exhibition
is just around the corner.
I don't think you've been
sleeping well at all these days.
But I guess it can't really be helped,
since you're working on your exhibition.
[chuckles]
Don't worry.
I'll catch a few winks through the night.
Any idea what
your next project's gonna be?
You know, once the exhibition's done.
Not really.
I haven't thought about it yet.
I see.
Hey. Maybe I'll take a break.
I can walk you to work
and then pick you up.
You got that new project, right?
How is it going?
Well, I guess it's going all right.
Not a lot of fun?
I only do it 'cause it's work.
Not really exciting stuff.
Hmm.
- [Ung] Yeon-su.
- Hmm?
When you get off work later--
Oh! No way. Look, it's Ung!
Damn this is nuts.
You're Ung and Yeon-su, right?
Watch your manners, you jackass.
They're literally 29 years old.
It's so nice to meet you.
We watched your documentary.
- We're big fans.
- Why are you together?
I thought you didn't like each other?
Was I wrong?
So was that whole thing scripted?
- No.
- They could've grown on each other.
[teenager 1] Oh, my god, you look
even way hotter in person!
[teenager 2] Can we take a photo, please?
It'll be quick.
- Well… Sure.
- [girls squealing]
[Myeong-ho] Stop. Right there.
That's me, right?
Damn, I look good.
Oh, they keep showing
the right side of my face,
when my left side is where I'm gorgeous.
Wow. Take a good look at Ms. Kook.
Charisma without trying.
Actually, between the two of them,
Ung is the one
who surprised me the most, you know.
- I know.
- I mean, compared to ten years ago
it's like, wow. You can never
really tell what the future has in store.
Look at them still yammering
at each other till now.
[co-workers chuckling]
[Myeong-ho] Honestly, I never
imagined she had this side of her.
Exactly. Although,
she's surprisingly cute when--
Okay, from now on
you're not allowed to watch or read
anything about that documentary at work.
And no talking about it either.
[all three] Got it.
Ms. Kook, what's going on over here, huh?
Where's my interview?
It's supposed to be there.
They cut it out? No way.
I asked for them to include it, because--
[Myeong-ho] We're banned
from talking about that.
- But I talked for an hour--
- It seems like we haven't been able
to focus on work lately. When in reality,
the Soen project should've been
our stepping stone to something greater.
I'm sure you're all aware where we are.
We haven't had a breakthrough
on our current project.
Right. That reminds me.
I meant to ask all of you,
you have any plans this evening?
Of course we don't.
We have work piled up so high
we can't even think about that.
Absolutely. I'm ready
to work till late tonight.
I even prepared
by wearing my comfortable pants.
Oh, me too. I'm staying behind
so I can assist everyone.
- And you, Mr. Bang?
- Huh?
Oh, that's right. I'm staying behind too.
It's not that.
I was thinking about treating everyone.
I mean, only if you guys are free tonight.
[Yeon-su] What do you say?
Actually…
Filming at work must have been
an inconvenience for everyone,
- so I wanna make it up--
- Hell yeah! I'd love that, Ms. Kook.
[I-hun] You can count me in.
Does that mean you'll be joining us today?
Like, actually be there?
I guess I could just pay for it--
- No.
- No. We didn't say that!
It's just, I don't think you've ever been
to our get-togethers.
This is a rare chance. I absolutely love
that idea. What do you guys think?
- Sounds great!
- I love it.
Am I in a dream? Someone pinch me.
Actually, don't. Where should we go?
- Ji-un, go look for the best food.
- I'll make sure to find one.
[I-hun] Let's get ready to clock out.
Gonna be a hell of an evening.
Gotta be fast and blast,
or you'll be last in the cast.
What should I do?
[Myeong-ho] Can you find
a nice chicken place?
[server] What bread
would you like with that?
Uh. Anything will do.
We'll have white bread and also
put some American cheese on that, please.
And toast it.
Are there any vegetables you don't like?
Me? Why do you ask?
Please put everything in one
and hold the olives on the other.
And the sauce. Which one would you like?
- Anything tasty will do.
- Mix the ranch and onion.
But not too much onion, please. Thank you.
Jeez.
- [Ung] Hey.
- All you need to do here is pay.
Christ. What would you do without me?
You've been awake
at this hour a lot more often.
You give up on sleeping entirely?
Uh-uh. I sleep a bit at night,
thanks to Yeon-su.
You never took my advice seriously before.
But now that she's talking,
suddenly you're listening.
Well, aren't you the romantic prick?
Ung, I'm rejecting all the interview
and magazine offers coming in.
Focus on the exhibition.
I guess people
really enjoyed the documentary, huh?
I've been getting offers
from TV shows left and right.
Reject them all.
Some of them actually want
both you and Yeon-su on their show.
Should I reject them too?
I'll ask her first. Maybe it's okay.
This is exactly why I refuse to date.
You have no right to decide on your own.
It's like giving up autonomy on your life.
What now? You're planning to do
whatever she tells you to?
[Ung] Hey.
What kind of person
do you think I come off as?
Hmm?
Do I look like I'm clueless?
Like I'm lost or aimless?
Hopeless is the word you're looking for.
Was that an actual serious question?
- What happened? Yeon-su nag you about it?
- She didn't.
Just, I wonder
if she never had expectations for me.
What are you saying?
Even I know that I'm…
I guess irresponsible and stuff.
[Ung] Not exactly reliable either.
That's why she doesn't think
she can rely on me when it matters.
Bro. Five years ago,
you said you'd succeed, whatever it takes.
Now, look how far you've come since then.
You really think you're irresponsible
after all this? You're not.
Plus, mind you, I have high standards.
Can't you see that I'm basically
devoting my entire twenties to you?
What's the matter with you?
[scoffs]
You didn't have to flatter me like that.
Look, I got no idea
what's gotten into you recently,
but I guess it's true, you're a bit
of an oddball and awfully childish too.
I'm what?
But you're an impressive guy.
Well, at least to me.
[scoffs]
I don't need to impress anyone.
Especially you.
Plus, can't you see
I'm pretty much relying on you?
You give me a monthly salary, you pay
for my food and my living expenses.
[sighs]
What's up, Ji-ung.
Heard your documentary was a success.
Shit, I'm jealous, little punk.
- Do you want one?
- Yeah, that'd be great.
How's your project going, bro?
You know, I think it's going well,
then again I'm not so sure.
Why? Is something wrong?
Do you know NJ well? The pop idol?
Somehow I must have gotten
the wrong impression of that girl.
- Why?
- [producer] I mean, she's a bit…
cooky.
It's the tenth anniversary
of her debut as an idol,
but she sounds like an aged singer
who's about to retire soon.
She seems pretty out of it
let me tell you.
Not a rare occurrence,
I've seen many people like her.
Every single time,
they just end up causing trouble.
- Really?
- We'll keep shooting, it's not impossible,
but damn,
I just hope she doesn't cause too much
trouble till we wrap up the thing.
Oh yeah, I got a recording to finish.
It's a narration. Gotta go.
Anyway, I'll see you around.
You better treat me to lunch sometime.
Okay.
[producer] See you.
[breathes in sharply]
"After driving down an empty road,
I arrived at this place."
"I spend what little my free time I have
doing what I want to do to relax my mind."
"I haven't enjoyed my leisure time
in a long while."
[soft pensive music]
Uh, NJ?
Oh, sorry, I lost focus.
Oh, don't worry.
That's fine. Let's do a retake.
"These are the moments you relish.
Spending some time by myself is bliss."
[NJ] "But whenever I go
to nice places or have good food,
I can't help but feel like I wanna spend
those moments with my friends around."
Is anything wrong? Keep going.
I can't, because the script is wrong.
Oh, which part do you mean?
I don't have any friends.
Sorry?
Do people really think about their friends
- in that situation?
- [producer] Oh.
Yeah, you make a good point.
So should we change that to "family"?
[gentle pensive music]
[humming]
Oh, sorry, we're not open yet.
Come back at five…
[tense music]
How have you been?
My dear Sol.
[tense music]
Where do you get the balls
to show your face around here, Jin-seob?
[Jin-seob] I know you're happy
to see me again,
- don't pretend like you're not.
- Who? Me?
Give me a single reason
why I'd I be happy to see you?
I know you've missed me so much.
You're a freaking psycho!
You think that asshole's
watching this right now?
Hey, Jin-seob.
Are you watching this? See all this?
Look at me. Guess what? A group
of ten people made reservations today.
I'm doing just fine.
I hope you're doing fine too.
So what?
You're not over me either.
Exactly which part
in that video gave you that impression?
I can tell just by looking at your face.
After all this time I had no idea
you'd send me a video letter.
You're still so adorable.
Get lost.
[cheeky music]
[Eun-ho] Sol-i.
Oh, you have a customer.
Someone scribbled
some stuff over your sign outside.
- You have acetone?
- Sure.
A part-timer?
Oh, no. I'm not. I don't work here.
I guess he's not a customer,
didn't know he was a friend of yours.
Hey. I said, get lost.
[chuckles]
I knew it.
You sure have a lot of guys, hmm?
- New boyfriend?
- That's ridiculous.
You better watch your mouth right now--
Hi, I'm her ex-boyfriend. And who are you?
I…
Hey, Kim Jin-seob. Can you just get lost?
You're kicking me out
right after calling me over?
What are you freaking crazy?
I never wanted to see you
in the first place.
Okay. Then let's talk
after you close down.
I'll be waiting somewhere close.
Can you just cut the crap? Just get lost.
Why don't you scram
before I really get violent.
[Jin-seob] Hey, Sol.
I really missed you. Genuinely.
I'll call you later.
Goodbye.
[cheeky music]
What are you doing here?
Hey. If you keep coming here, I might
have to start giving you a paycheck.
What do you do all day? You might as well
hand in a resume pretty soon.
Any reason your ex paid you a visit?
No, but who knows?
Whatever. Guy's a psychopath.
[cheeky music]
[Sol-i chopping angrily]
- What?
- Where's the acetone? Hurry up.
Right. Acetone.
Now, where did I put that?
I think it's over there, isn't it?
Hmm. Feels like you own the place.
POTATO SOUP WITH UNG
- Hey, Dad.
- Oh, my goodness.
Oh gosh, you startled me.
I heard Mom caught you
pocketing some money for your hobby.
Is your mom still upset at me?
Are you just waiting for her
to kick you out of the house?
Stop buying more fishing rods.
You realize how many you already have?
That's rich, coming from you
the one who broke so many of them
that I have to keep going out to buy some.
It's not like they're all the same,
each one has a different feel to it.
I really wanted to catch a big fish
this time around. I know how to do it.
But if only I had that fishing rod…
[sighs]
Just forget it.
You always side
with your mom anyway, you little traitor.
Don't you have savings or something?
[huffs]
Mr. Choi, I pity you, I truly do.
What are you doing?
Don't tell me you came
all the way here to make fun of me.
[chuckles softly]
Watch it.
What are you getting so close for?
Come on.
Just open your pocket and put this in.
[Ho] What? Why? What is it?
What? Hey. Wow.
Don't let her know, okay?
Buy that rod and hide it
where no one can ever see it.
Because if she ever finds out,
it's my butt on the line as well.
- Oh, gosh! My sweet boy!
- Dad, she's going to find out.
That rod is actually very expensive.
I know. So I made sure to give you enough.
Oh, my sweet little boy…
But seriously.
You really didn't need to do this.
I would have been fine.
It's just a fishing rod.
- Do you even have enough?
- What?
Look, Dad, your son earns quite a bit.
[chuckles proudly]
You stayed up for days to earn this money.
You've grown up so much I barely know you.
All right come on, get on my back.
- On my back!
- Oh, don't get all affectionate.
[groans]
Oh, my gosh.
Oh? It's Chang-sik. Chang-sik!
Chang-sik. Oh, Chang-sik.
Hey, check it out. My son right there.
Look how much money he gave me
so I could get that fishing rod. Look!
[gasps]
Hey, Yeon-ok!
Whoa, hey! What are you doing?
Wait! You're gonna get me killed! Stop it!
Oh.
[soft music]
[NJ] Mr. Kim?
That was you back there, wasn't it?
Uhm, yeah. Did you finish recording yet?
Not yet, took a break.
I'm waiting for them
to revise a few things first
then I'll get back to it.
[NJ] That's why I'm just waiting around.
I noticed you never seem to
ever have a proper dinner.
Oh, right. Have you eaten yet?
No, I can't eat. I'm on a strict diet.
But if you're gonna be eating alone,
maybe I can join you?
Seeing people eating
by themselves breaks my heart.
Sure, okay. I'm not gonna stop you.
I'm a bit busy,
so I was gonna eat alone anyway.
What are the things you usually
think about when you're eating alone?
Hmm…
I think about the amount
of rice and side dishes left
'cause I have to calculate.
I have to finish them at the same time.
I agree.
Did you hear that thing I said
about thinking of your friends
when I was recording?
I mean, who thinks about their friends
while they're eating?
You don't, you just eat.
By the way,
you don't have any friends, do you?
I don't, because my situation
doesn't allow for it.
[NJ] I've been working
way back since I was young,
so you can imagine
there are things I can't have
that seem like a given most people.
It's not even easy to make friends with
someone you've worked with for a while.
Most of all,
I don't have time to meet new people.
That's why I just gave up making friends.
[Ji-ung] You know what?
If you wanna live
an ordinary life like other people,
then just pretend like you are.
I know it seems
like a difficult thing to do,
but it's all about your state of mind.
And maybe after some time,
you'll find that
you don't even have to pretend.
We can't always
just blame our surroundings.
We're talking about our lives,
it can't just stop there.
Thinking that way just holds you back.
So you ought to give it a shot.
At least before giving up entirely,
you should give yourself a chance.
A chance, that's all.
[gentle music]
[chuckles softly]
Since that last time…
you've had a habit
of comforting me out of the blue.
Really?
Have you ever considered
that we're both in the same situation?
[breathes in sharply]
Maybe it's true.
You receive a monthly rent,
while I receive a monthly payment.
[both chuckling]
So what's Mr. Choi up to nowadays?
[chuckles softly]
I saw that coming a mile away.
[groans]
I'm dying to know what he's up to,
but I acted all tough and said
I wasn't gonna call or visit him anymore.
[NJ sighs]
You see?
He never calls me first, it's always me.
If I stopped trying,
he wouldn't have even cared or noticed.
So tell me. I just wanna know,
what he's up to these days.
I'm not sure.
The two of us haven't met in a while.
Why not? Did you have a fight?
I think we're too old for that.
Then?
[soft pensive music]
[sighs]
Oh. I think I should get going.
Thank you for keeping me company
while I had dinner.
Bye.
[NJ] Dine and dash?
Come on. Would it have hurt
to answer that last one?
[sighs]
Mm. Hey, Ung.
I have a company get-together.
Yeah, I know.
I never used to attend these things.
I wanted to make it up to them
because I felt bad for filming at work.
[chuckles softly]
Should have never said yes to that thing.
Such an inconvenience these days.
[all cheering]
Yeah, chicken, yeah!
- Wow.
- Thank you.
Oh, by the way, are you sure
Ms. Ji couldn't make it
because she suddenly felt sick?
She's really sick.
Shame, she loves attending get-togethers.
She was crying when we left work.
That's why we need to
take care of ourselves these days.
[breathes in sharply]
Too bad, she should really be here.
Oh well, let's just enjoy this meal, okay?
By the way, this is pretty unbelievable.
I never thought
that this day would ever come.
I mean,
I didn't even propose this get-together.
Ms. Kook made the proposal,
she took that initiative of inviting us.
Am I right? Right. Eat up and drink lots!
Why do you seem so ecstatic?
Is it because she's the one
who's buying all this?
Ms. Kook and myself are one.
We act in unison.
We are one team and one body.
She represents our company.
So you pretty much knew it.
She's basically
the real boss of the company.
- All right, everyone. Cheers.
- Yeah, cheers.
[satisfied groan]
Not bad. This place makes great beer.
By the way, how'd you manage to keep
Ms. Kook by your side all this time?
Hmm? What do you mean?
She's like a phenom.
We all know how competent she is.
I'm sure lots of companies
tried to poach her repeatedly.
Oh, you mean that?
I was her senior back in school.
- Really? University?
- Haven't I told you that?
[I-hun] We were in the same club.
As for me, I was the chairman of our club.
[I-hun chuckles]
She was deeply moved by my leadership,
also my creative
and innovative way of thinking
that's always ahead of the curve.
That's basically
why she's working with me.
[all chuckling]
Wait a second. How does that work?
You went to university with her
- but the age gap--
- It's smaller than you think.
- Trust me on that.
- Oh.
Anyway, Ms. Kook, she was
already impressive, even back then.
You could just tell.
I have never seen anyone work as hard
in life as she does every single day.
You shouldn't be talking about someone
while they're gone, it's not polite.
Yeah, I know.
Don't go anywhere from now on.
All right. Now that she's here,
why don't we have a drink together?
Glasses up, come on.
[guys] Cheers.
[cheerful music]
[I-hun] Ms. Kook.
I saved you your favorite piece
since you're the one treating us tonight.
Oh, thank you. That's nice.
[I-hun] It feels so good.
We're finally having
our first get-together with Ms. Kook
after all this time.
Okay, now promise me
none of you are going home tonight.
Promise me. Come on, do it.
Wow, that just proves to us
how happy he is right now.
But we should still go home.
It's true, having Ms. Kook here
is like a special event.
We can't help but get
a little more excited than usual.
I agree with that. I love that she's here.
In fact, we should do every now and then.
I'd like to make a toast
to mark this occasion.
Okay. Here's to the real awakening of--
That's enough.
Go, you're the youngest one.
Sure. Don't just walk! Run!
[guys] Run!
[Myeong-ho] That's refreshing.
- [Ji-un] That's a really good beer.
- [I-hun] It's okay.
All right, where was I? So we're both
at the same university right…
[bright music]
[huffs]
Are you waiting for someone?
Who? Me? For who? I'm not.
Looked like you were waiting.
You must have been waiting
for your ex, am I right?
You serious? Obviously not.
You saw what happened earlier,
he came here
because he couldn't get over me.
I didn't wanna see him.
I do admit though,
it's a little difficult to get over me.
That's why they all
have a tough time trying to forget.
But it's not like it's my fault.
I wasn't asking.
Frankly, none of what he said
actually bothered me
especially when he said he'd wait.
I have no intention
of getting back with him,
but I can tell that he's suffering.
It was in his eyes.
So if he came back,
I was gonna comfort him and send him home.
I still wasn't asking you.
Sheesh.
Right. Good timing. Glad you're here.
I have to give something to the shop
next door, so just stay here, please.
I need to go. I can't stay here.
It's not gonna take long.
- [Eun-ho] You better hurry or else…
- Uh-huh.
Thank you!
[Eun-ho sighs]
From blind date to an ex-boyfriend…
She should focus on her job.
Why are there so many guys around her?
[Eun-ho sighing]
She didn't empty the trash again.
[groans]
Why does she have to be
such a handful anyway?
[sighs]
Always gotta be the people around me.
For once, I wanna meet someone
who doesn't need my help.
LEEZAKAYA
[sighs]
[Jin-seob] I'm telling you. I think
I can borrow at least five million won.
Business seems to be doing well.
I can get the money right away.
It's Sol-i. I can't remember
her ever saying no to me.
Right when we met. Had her under my spell.
Just gotta nudge her right.
She'll give in as usual.
She may look all apathetic
but she can be quite gullible too.
[tense music]
Hang on a second.
[awkward chuckle]
You're that guy from earlier.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Who told you all that?
All that…
Yeah, about Sol-i.
Who said her bar was doing well?
[gasps]
Oh no, it's late.
I feel so bad.
I should feed Eun-ho before he leaves.
[Eun-ho] You understand?
What the heck is he doing here?
Just so you know,
Sol-i's not yours anymore.
What the hell? Is he crazy?
[suspenseful music]
'Cause as of now…
she belongs to the bank. You know?
Is it that bad?
How many loans did she take out?
Really bad. She's neck-deep.
She'll ever be able to pay it back.
Or at least not in this life.
I thought business was going well.
Oh, don't get me started.
The shrimp she had delivered yesterday
outnumber the customers
who came last month.
I shouldn't have come here.
You're right about that.
[inhales]
Anyway, thank you for the tip-off.
[Jin-seob sighs]
Wait, where are you going?
You're not gonna wait?
What for? To break our hearts?
My dear Sol. Take good care of her.
[cheeky music]
[chuckles]
Hey, you're late.
You said it wouldn't take long.
So?
Any customers come in?
You know, none as usual.
No one came, nothing new there.
[sweet music]
What? Say something.
What the heck are you doing?
Nothing.
[phone buzzing]
Perfect timing. We just said our goodbyes.
[Ung] How much did you drink?
[chuckles]
Not much. A little.
[Ung] Are you going home now?
Mm-hmm.
[Ung] I wanted to pick you up,
but felt you wouldn't like it.
Really? I wouldn't?
[Ung] Mm-hmm. You used to say
that you'd be embarrassed
if I came to pick you up
when you could've walked home.
You wanted to be independent.
[chuckles softly]
I can't believe you still remember that.
[Ung] Mm-hmm.
I can remember all sorts of things.
[gentle music]
But you know back then,
I only said all that stuff because
I didn't wanna take up your time.
Also, I didn't want you spending
so much money on those taxi fares.
Back then, I even thought
taking a cab was too expensive.
I was scared of you spending.
[Ung] Not because
you didn't want me to come to see you?
Mm-hmm.
[Ung] Understood. Now look behind you.
Hmm?
From now on,
please tell me these things in advance.
[sweet happy music]
Because if you don't tell me,
I won't figure it out.
I'm stupid like that.
["Summer Rain" by Sam Kim playing]
[Ung] I'm still not sure why we broke up.
I'm stupid like that.
Promise me…
you'll tell me everything.
Hmm.
[Ung] I'm sure will…
she'll tell me one day.
Because being patient
is something I'm very good at.
Everything you tell me sticks with me.
I remember all of it.
So just keep telling me.
Understood.
[Ung] Someday, I'll find out the reason.
And once I do, I'll do everything I can
to make sure it never happens again.
Shall we?
That's what I've decided.
It'll be my main goal in life.
Wow. Look at all those stars.
You cold?
Yeon-su, I wanna be with you forever.
[gentle music]
ENROLLMENT GUIDE
SCHOOL OF ARCHITECTURE
[deep sigh]
PREPARING FOR STUDYING
AT A FRENCH ARCHITECTURE SCHOOL
FRENCH GRADUATE SCHOOL
LYONE UNIVERSITY
[gentle music]
MEDICAL SERVICE
SPECIALTIES
[soft emotional music]
[Ja-gyeong] What is all this?
You prepared a feast for breakfast.
There's so much here. Hmm.
Goodness. You even grilled some fish?
Good grief.
Oh wow, that's great.
- [Ja-gyeong] The fish looks good.
- How is it?
Mm-hmm.
Is it good?
What gives? It's really delicious.
[chuckles]
Have some of this.
Go ahead and eat. I can eat on my own.
[chuckles softly]
Do you want to go on a trip somewhere?
Hmm? Just like that? Out of the blue?
My legs wouldn't be able to handle it.
Come on.
Wherever it is, we can drive there.
It's starting to get colder now.
Let's go to a hot spring
and get some well-earned R and R.
I'll take a few days off from work.
We can go sightseeing and stuff.
We'll eat lots of good food
from everywhere.
What's gotten into you?
I'll grill your favorite fish as many
times as you want, among other dishes.
We can go out on many trips.
I swear, and I'll buy you all
the pretty clothes that you'll ever want.
You can go to the welfare center
and brag about it.
We'll do that.
Let's live together forever.
[soft vulnerable music]
As long as you don't go anywhere,
you need to be by my side.
Understand?
["Home" by Janet Suhh playing]
Yeon-su…
Don't you like living with me, Grandma?
What are you talking about?
[in shaky voice]
Don't you?
You like it, right?
I know you care about me, it's just…
Everyone else might not feel the same way…
but not you.
Because I know you like me for who I am.
Of course. How could I ever not like you?
Exactly.
So please…
don't go anywhere without telling me.
Stay by my side.
I…
I just don't ever
want to feel lonely again.
["Home" by Janet Suhh continuing]
[sobs]
LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL
EPILOGUE
[Ji-ung's mom] You're home.
You're back a lot sooner than I expected.
I thought I'd see you again
after a few seasons.
We need to talk.
I'm tired. Next time.
[Ji-ung's mom] You work
at the media, right?
You know, filming those shows…
[sighs]
How did you know that?
Because I can't imagine you ever caring
about what I did for a living.
Please just be yourself.
- You don't need to know--
- [Ji-ung's mom] I heard…
anyone could participate
in the type of stuff you do.
Someone who has absolutely nothing.
Common people. Ordinary.
Just what are you going on about?
I want you to do a shoot on me.
[humorless chuckle]
You want me to do a shoot on who?
Me.
You can do that, can't you?
[sighs]
Get some rest.
I'm gonna go and do the same.
[Ji-ung's mom] I'm dying.
Apparently…
["Home" by Janet Suhh playing]
…I don't have long to live.
I was wondering…
if you could film me before I die.
Can you?